nenablue.com 2011-11-30

# Untitled Document

In order to provide Internet billing services, CCBill must collect, use, and share certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, who we share it with, and how you can contact CCBill in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect, use, and share. The information CCBill collects from you helps CCBill better serve you and the online community by continually updating the electronic payment services CCBill provides. The data that CCBill collects and maintains is as follows: 

**Information that you provide to us**  
CCBill receives and stores all information that you enter on our sign-up (join) pages except for security items such as Visa’s CVV2. This includes:

**1\. Credit card sign-up page** \- the website you are purchasing an e-ticket for, your e-mail address, language preference, credit card number, expiration date, first name, last name, address, city, state, zip, country, your username and password, and your agreement to be bound by CCBill 's terms and conditions.

**2\. Check sign-up page** \- the website you are purchasing an e-ticket for, your e-mail address, language preference, first name, last name, address, city, state, zip, country, your bank's ABA routing number, your account number, the type of account, your username and password, and your agreement to be bound by CCBill 's terms and conditions.

**Information that we automatically receive**  
CCBill receives and stores certain information whenever you download web pages, or send us e-mail or forms. For example:

1\. We identify the numerical IP address assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider.

2\. E-mail Correspondence: CCBill often requests a confirmation when you receive and open an e-mail communication delivered by CCBill. We archive all e-mail sent in and out of our network, and we identify the origination IP address of all mail sent into our network. We require that you refrain from "forging headers" or sending "SPAM". 

**Information from third parties**  
From time to time, CCBill may request and receive information from third parties and compare it to the information that you have provided. The main purpose for this is loss prevention.

**Protection of your privacy**  
CCBill will release data when we believe the release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Agreement, and protect the contract rights of our Clients. CCBill passes the following data to the owner/operator of the website from which you are purchasing services utilizing CCBill’s services:

1\. Credit card sign-up page information including the website you are purchasing an e-ticket for, your e-mail address, language preference, first name, last name, address, city, state, zip, country, your username and password, and your agreement to be bound by CCBill 's terms and conditions. 

2\. Check sign-up page information including the website you are purchasing an e-ticket for, your e-mail address, language preference, first name, last name, address, city, state, zip, country, your username and password, and your agreement to be bound by CCBill's terms and conditions.

It is your obligation to provide CCBill with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide us with such information could void any Agreement between you and CCBill. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as processing your e-ticket request, responding to customer service inquiries, loss prevention, improving our service, communicating with you, and allowing our clients to provide customer service and fulfill their obligations to you. CCBill’s employees have access to your information on a need-to-know basis. CCBill will not sell your information to an independent third party for any reason.

In addition, CCBill, as part of the credit card processing system must provide limited information to the services that connect it to the companies that perform the banking functions. The credit card associations have strict privacy rules that these companies must adhere to in order to be authorized to receive and process credit card transactions. CCBill will never knowingly provide your credit card or bank account information outside of this system.

CCBill employs the latest and best techniques available for protecting its systems from intrusion by unauthorized individuals, and is constantly upgrading its security as better methods become available. All information is stored behind firewalls and other sophisticated security systems. In addition, our data center utilizes state-of-the-art physical security measures to prevent unauthorized access to the facility.

CCBill does not request, or knowingly collect identifiable information from children under the age of 18. CCBill does not knowingly use or share personal information from users under the age of 18 with third parties. CCBill does not offer children any promotions involving games, prizes, or any other activity that would induce a child to divulge personal information.

CCBill reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. CCBill takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. We will occasionally update our privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy policy updates.  
Questions regarding the information CCBill has stored about you should be in writing, and addressed to:

**CCBill LLC  
1501 West 17th Street  
Tempe, Arizona 85281 – U.S.A.  
Phone (480) 449-7750   
Fax (480) 449- 8819**
